<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Design on Chris Gallo | What They Said</title>
    <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/categories/design/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Design on Chris Gallo | What They Said</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/categories/design/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Beth Dunn</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/beth-dunn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/beth-dunn/</guid>
      <description>Beth Dunn shares how to use your words. You&amp;rsquo;ve likely heard her 10 tips before. But Beth really explains these in detail with techniques on how and why to do these things.
She believes we don&amp;rsquo;t spend enough time thinking about how we sound. We only think about why we want to say. Check out the excerpt below and 10 tips at the bottom of this post. Watch the talk here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julie Zhuo</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/julie-zhuo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/julie-zhuo/</guid>
      <description>Julie Zhuo chats with Bryn Jackson and Brian Lovin of the Design Details podcast. Julie shares her path from being Facebook&amp;rsquo;s first intern to leading design on a product that is used by billions of people.
Below is a transcribed excerpt, but the whole interview is full of useful advice. Be sure to check out some of Julie&amp;rsquo;s writing too :)
What is being a manager about? Over the years, what I really enjoy is working with designers and really helping designers become better designers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Torrey Podmajersky</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/torrey-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/torrey-p/</guid>
      <description>This a talk delivered by Torrey Podmajersky at the 2015 Write the Docs conference. Torrey is a UI writer for Microsoft. She has worked on Xbox and other projects that are used by millions of people. Torrey sprinkles in dynamite examples about how to keep people moving when using your product. Check out the full video here and excerpts below.
What is UI Text? 00:56 I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you about these two cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merlinn Mann</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/merlinn-mann/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/merlinn-mann/</guid>
      <description>Merlin Mann shares some wisdom in this talk delivered at the E4E Developer Conference in 2014. It&amp;rsquo;s inspiring, funny, honest, damn good advice on how to get better at whatever you do. Below are excerpts, but the entire talk is worth a watch and listen.
Better is elusive: 3:20 I find it very hard to get better at things. I find it very difficult to do. I think a lot of people struggle with it for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samuel Hulick</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/samuel-hulick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/samuel-hulick/</guid>
      <description>This is conversation between Samuel Hulick and Justin Jackson on Product People TV. Samuel shares how he built User Onboarding and what he&amp;rsquo;s learned along the way. Lots of useful examples of how to treat customers like human beings. Check out the full conversation here.
##How Did You Start User Onboarding
My friend Jane Portman has an analogy that I use all the time, which is &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s like having your suitcase packed with no handle on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pamela Slim</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/pamela-slim/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/pamela-slim/</guid>
      <description>This a conversation between Pamela Slim and Sean Blanda on the 99U podcast. Lately, if I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about reading a certain book, I&amp;rsquo;ll look for a podcast or interview with the author to learn more about it. This a perfect example.
Sean and Pamela discuss her book, Body of Work: Finding the Thread That Ties Your Story Together. After listening, I&amp;rsquo;ve added this one to my list to read in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gina Redish</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gina-redish/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gina-redish/</guid>
      <description>Ginny Redish is the author of Letting Go of the Words: Writing Web Content that Works. She is a pioneer in how to communicate on the web. Ginny has helped companies like IBM communicate with customers and teaches people why content is conversation.
Check out the full conversation with her and Kristina Halvorson on the Content Talks podcast. And find a short excerpt below.
Content as Conversation If you think about it, in a typical website, your site just doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist until somebody comes to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicole Fenton</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/nicole-fenton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/nicole-fenton/</guid>
      <description>Nicole Fenton is a guest on the Happy Monday Podcast with Josh Long and Sarah Parmenter. Nicole designs with words. She is excellent communicator working with companies from Apple to Facebook. The trio talks her book, Nicely Said, co-authored with Kate Kiefer Lee and other philosophies behind writing. Listen to the full conversation here.
Starting from the bottom I knew I wanted to be a writer when I was very young.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rena Tom</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/rena-tom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/rena-tom/</guid>
      <description>This is a Pencil vs. Pixel conversation between Rena Tom and Cesar Contreras. Pencil vs. Pixel, hosted by Cesar, is a weekly web show that shares insight, advice, and inspiration about creative work. Rena is a consultant and the market editor for Anthology magazine. Plus she is the founder of Makeshift Society, a clubhouse and creative co-working space in San Francisco and Brooklyn. Check out an excerpt below and listen to the full conversation as Rena shares her story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brad Frost</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/brad-frost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/brad-frost/</guid>
      <description>The following is a TEDx talk with Brad Frost. The web designer, writer, and speaker delivers a perspective about why you should share what you create across the web. You should check out his blog and his Death to Bullshit talk about craft. Check out the full TEDx video here.
How the Web Changed Creation Because it was so expensive to create, the focus was always on the final product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tina Roth Eisenberg</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/tina-roth-eisenberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/tina-roth-eisenberg/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from a 2-part series on mentor lessons with Tina Roth Eisenberg. Tina shares tips to success for Shopify&amp;rsquo;s 2013 Build a Business Competition. Special thanks to Shopify for hosting the video. Watch part 1 and part 2.
The Best Way to Complain Don&amp;rsquo;t be a complainer, make things better. I have this personal rule that if I find myself complaining about this same thing over and over again, I need to either let it go or do something about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debbie Millman</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/debbie-millman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/debbie-millman/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from a conversation between Debbie Millman and Jonathan Fields for the Good Life Project. Millman shares her career path and wisdom on how to find purpose in your life. Watch and listen to the full episode here.
Do what you want I teach seniors in college. And my class is about getting a job. But it&amp;rsquo;s about getting the job of your dreams. Not just getting a job to pay the rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessica Hische</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jessica-hische/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jessica-hische/</guid>
      <description>This is a Creative Mornings talk with Jessica Hische in Vancouver. Hische delivers about a 10 minute rant sans slides that is amazing. The majority of the excerpt is in the beginning, but you hang on for a great conversation about type. Watch and listen to the full video here.
Mandatory Everyone knows as soon as you make something mandatory, it becomes the opposite of what you want to do for a living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stanley Hainsworth</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/stanley-hainsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/stanley-hainsworth/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from a 2010 conversation between Stanley Hainsworth and Robert Scoble. Hainsworth shares his path to storytelling and his agency Tether. Special thanks to Scoble and Rackspace for hosting the video. Watch the full conversation here.
Brands are People I always equate brands as people. You could describe what Apple is as a person. Because of the personality they&amp;rsquo;ve created.
So with companies, the first thing I do is say lets figure out what your story is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Sierra</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kathy-sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kathy-sierra/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from 2010 Gov 2.0 Expo with Kathy Sierra. She has given this talk several times and spread the message on her blog. Special thanks to O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media for hosting the video. Watch the full talk here.
Kicking Ass Where there is passion, there are people kicking ass. People don&amp;rsquo;t sustain passion for things they continue to suck at.
One of the reasons that passion is compelling for people is because when they are pursing something, learning and growing - they start to have a higher resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from the 1997 Apple Worldwide Developers Conference. An hour long Q &amp;amp; A, it includes nuggets of brilliance that still are true 17 years later. Special thanks to mactechlab for posting it to YouTube, and to Semil for sharing the video. Watch the full talk here.
Focus: 5:55 When you think about focusing, you think focusing is saying yes. Focusing is about saying no. Focusing is about saying no.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>