<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philosophy on Chris Gallo | What They Said</title>
    <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/categories/philosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Philosophy on Chris Gallo | What They Said</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/categories/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Nassim Nicholas Taleb</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/nassim-nicholas-taleb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/nassim-nicholas-taleb/</guid>
      <description>Nassim Nicholas Taleb gives a short introduction to the idea of antifragility. This concept is covered in length in Taleb&amp;rsquo;s book, Antifragile Thingss That Gain From Disorder. It&amp;rsquo;s part of a series of books from Taleb. The others are Fooled by Randomness, The Black Swan, and The Bed of Procrustes.
This book and interview are difficult to understand. It&amp;rsquo;s quite the idea and concept, but Taleb knows that too. I&amp;rsquo;ve found a few great summaries here that can help: Max Mednik&amp;rsquo;s extensive notes, notes from Nat Alison and four minute book notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbara Oakley</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/barbara-oakley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/barbara-oakley/</guid>
      <description>Jacob Taylor asks Barbara Oakley 5 Good Questions. Barbara has written several books on psychology and learning. I was more interested in some concepts from her book, A Mind for Numbers.
The book centers around how to excel at math or science, but really it&amp;rsquo;s a book about learning how we learn. There are a lot of useful techniques, here is a solid summary. She touches on several of these in this short interview, and some bits are transcribed below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gordon Livingston</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gordon-livingston/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gordon-livingston/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Livingston was a psychiatrist and author who wrote several books on being human. This transcription is a conversation related to his book, Too Soon Old, Too Late Smart: Thirty True Things You Need to Know Now. It&amp;rsquo;s hosted by Dan Rodricks on WYPR.
Livingston passed away in March of 2016. He had some incredible life experiences, and listening to him or reading his books makes you feel smarter than you already are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omar Zenhom</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/omar-zenhom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/omar-zenhom/</guid>
      <description>Omar Zenhom shares a quick review of Edward de Bono&amp;rsquo;s book, Six Thinking Hats, on the $100 MBA podcast. The framework presented by de Bono is practical and useful when making decisions.
Listen to Zenhom&amp;rsquo;s 15 minute review here, and check out a short transcription and graphic below.
Why the Framework? 2:40 As Edward de Bono explains in his book, thinking is the ultimate human resource. Yet, we can never be satisfied with our most important skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>William Ury</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/william-ury/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/william-ury/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation between William Ury and Simon Sinek. The two discuss Ury&amp;rsquo;s new book, Getting to Yes with Yourself, and other negotiation tips.
It&amp;rsquo;s a dense back-and-forth, so you might find yourself rewinding the video a bit like I did. Sinek adds a lot with his questions (listen to his TED talk if you haven&amp;rsquo;t before) and shares his own experiences too. Check out the excerpt below and the video here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merlinn Mann</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/merlinn-mann/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/merlinn-mann/</guid>
      <description>Merlin Mann shares some wisdom in this talk delivered at the E4E Developer Conference in 2014. It&amp;rsquo;s inspiring, funny, honest, damn good advice on how to get better at whatever you do. Below are excerpts, but the entire talk is worth a watch and listen.
Better is elusive: 3:20 I find it very hard to get better at things. I find it very difficult to do. I think a lot of people struggle with it for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessica Lawrence </title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jessica-lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jessica-lawrence/</guid>
      <description>Jessica Lawrence shares a story about leadership. From high school to the Girl Scouts of the USA to NY Tech Meetup, Jessica connects the dots about what is needed to be a leader. I was directed to this video by Jeff Vincent. Check out his newsletter and subscribe here.
And take 10 minutes to listen to Jessica&amp;rsquo;s story.
Doing What You Think is Right Most of the time when I was in high school, it was a good thing to be featured in the school newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Kelly</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kevin-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kevin-kelly/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a conversation between Tim Ferriss and Kevin Kelly on the Tim Ferriss Show. A college dropout, Kevin shares his story of living overseas, doing LSD at 50 years old, and what he&amp;rsquo;s learned along the way. Kevin is the Senior Maverick at Wired Magazine and known for other projects like Cool Tools.
Below is an excerpt of a three-part conversation. It just scratches the surface. Make sure you listen to all three parts, as Ferriss says, &amp;ldquo;Kevin Kelly might be the real-life Most Interesting Man In The World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derek Sivers</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/derek-sivers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/derek-sivers/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation between Bob Baker and Derek Sivers on The Creative Entrepreneur podcast. Derek shares his background from circus ringleader to musician to million-dollar business owner at CD Baby to creating a book publishing company. You can learn a lot from his perspective and his book Anything You Want. Check out an excerpt below and watch or listen to the full conversation here.
Changing Your Operating System I&amp;rsquo;m a total Chicago boy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maria Popova</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/maria-popova/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/maria-popova/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation from the Employee of the Month podcast. Catie Lazarus and Maria Popova talk through life and learning. Popova curates an amazing blog called Brain Pickings and runs a discovery engine called Explore. It&amp;rsquo;s impossible not to find inspiration in her work and this talk. Listen to the full 45 minute conversation here and check out excerpts below.
How did Brain Pickings Start? What I do always has two components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clayton Christensen</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/clayton-christensen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/clayton-christensen/</guid>
      <description>This is a short excerpt from a conversation between Clayton Christensen and Tom Ashbrook on the On Point NPR radio show. Christensen is the co-author of How to Measure Your Life, a book that uses business and real-life examples to teach you lessons. Sandwiched between religious and political sidebars, there is thought-provoking conversation as Christensen answers questions from the audience. Listen to the full conversation here.
Where You Spend Your Resources Toyota didn&amp;rsquo;t come to America with the Lexus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Fried</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jason-fried/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jason-fried/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from Chicago Founders&amp;rsquo; Stories. Jason Fried shares the the story behind 37 Signals, Basecamp, and working with Jeff Bezos. Thanks to Pat Ryan and builtinchicago.org. Watch the entire interview here. The transcript starts at 1:18:30.
 I love listening to him, more than talking to him. I will give you one business thing and one life thing he told us.
 Business The most important thing in business is to figure out what&amp;rsquo;s not going to change in your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stanley Hainsworth</title>
      <link>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/stanley-hainsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/stanley-hainsworth/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from a 2010 conversation between Stanley Hainsworth and Robert Scoble. Hainsworth shares his path to storytelling and his agency Tether. Special thanks to Scoble and Rackspace for hosting the video. Watch the full conversation here.
Brands are People I always equate brands as people. You could describe what Apple is as a person. Because of the personality they&amp;rsquo;ve created.
So with companies, the first thing I do is say lets figure out what your story is.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>