<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chris Gallo | What They Said</title>
    <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chris Gallo | What They Said</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Belsky</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/scott-belsky/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/scott-belsky/</guid>
      <description>Scott Belsky shares some wise words on the Tim Ferriss show. Tim asks Scott a pair of questions, and Scott shares bad advice to avoid and good advice to follow.
Scott built Behance, which was later acquired by Adobe. He manages product for Adobe&amp;rsquo;s Creative Cloud. The interview starts at around the 37-minute mark, listen to it here.
What are bad recommendations you hear in your industry or area of expertise?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Veronica Belmont</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/veronica-belmont/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/veronica-belmont/</guid>
      <description>Veronica Belmont helps people understand how technology can better their lives. She is the product Manager at Disco, and involved in lots of other things across the web.
Veronica answers two questions from Tim Ferriss. Her responses are short, but powerful. You can listen to the answers on the Tim Ferriss show. Her interview starts at around the 43-minute mark.
What are some bad recommendations you hear in your industry?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jeff Bezos</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jeff-bezos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jeff-bezos/</guid>
      <description>Jeff Bezos is the Amazon.com Founder &amp;amp; CEO. This is a short chat brought to you by the Internet Association. The association&amp;rsquo;s President &amp;amp; CEO, Michael Beckerman, discusses business, the early days of Amazon, space, and the future.
It&amp;rsquo;s a conversation that gets more interesting as it goes on because it&amp;rsquo;s full of wisdom. Read through some bits and pieces below, and go watch the full 37-minute discussion here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kara Swisher</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kara-swisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kara-swisher/</guid>
      <description>Kara Swisher is a damn good journalist. She&amp;rsquo;s the co-founder of recode, went to school to be a spy, and known as the most well-liked and feared journalist in Silicon Valley.
Swisher joins Tim Ferriss&amp;rsquo; podcast to discuss the skills of a good reporter, her sexuality, parenting, tidbits of interviews with Steve Jobs, and more. This is a short transcription of a few bits I found interesting and useful. Listen to the full interview here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nassim Nicholas Taleb</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/nassim-nicholas-taleb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/nassim-nicholas-taleb/</guid>
      <description>Nassim Nicholas Taleb gives a short introduction to the idea of antifragility. This concept is covered in length in Taleb&amp;rsquo;s book, Antifragile Thingss That Gain From Disorder. It&amp;rsquo;s part of a series of books from Taleb. The others are Fooled by Randomness, The Black Swan, and The Bed of Procrustes.
This book and interview are difficult to understand. It&amp;rsquo;s quite the idea and concept, but Taleb knows that too. I&amp;rsquo;ve found a few great summaries here that can help: Max Mednik&amp;rsquo;s extensive notes, notes from Nat Alison and four minute book notes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barbara Oakley</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/barbara-oakley/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/barbara-oakley/</guid>
      <description>Jacob Taylor asks Barbara Oakley 5 Good Questions. Barbara has written several books on psychology and learning. I was more interested in some concepts from her book, A Mind for Numbers.
The book centers around how to excel at math or science, but really it&amp;rsquo;s a book about learning how we learn. There are a lot of useful techniques, here is a solid summary. She touches on several of these in this short interview, and some bits are transcribed below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shep Gordon</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/shep-gordon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/shep-gordon/</guid>
      <description>Shep Gordon joins the Art of Charm podcast. Shep discusses life lessons from his book, They Call Me Supermensch. If you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen the documentary, Supermensch, you&amp;rsquo;re missing out. It&amp;rsquo;s full of fantastic stories and it&amp;rsquo;s incredibly entertaining.
Shep is known as the manager of Alice Cooper, Teddy Pendergrass, Luther Vandross, and many more. He&amp;rsquo;s the godfather of the celebrity chef movement, and has worked with several world class chefs like Roger Vergé and Emeril Lagasse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karen Dillon</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/karen-dillon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/karen-dillon/</guid>
      <description>Karen Dillon talks jobs-to-be-done at the Stern Strategy Group. Karen has co-authored a couple books, How to Measure Your Life and Competing Against Luck: The Story of Innovation and Customer Choice, with Clayton Christensen and others.
The first 8 minutes or so of the talk wasn&amp;rsquo;t all that new to me. It includes some dynamite anecdotes from How to Measure Your Life, like the job-to-be-done of a dining room table via Bob Moesta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gordon Livingston</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gordon-livingston/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gordon-livingston/</guid>
      <description>Gordon Livingston was a psychiatrist and author who wrote several books on being human. This transcription is a conversation related to his book, Too Soon Old, Too Late Smart: Thirty True Things You Need to Know Now. It&amp;rsquo;s hosted by Dan Rodricks on WYPR.
Livingston passed away in March of 2016. He had some incredible life experiences, and listening to him or reading his books makes you feel smarter than you already are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miki Agrawal</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/miki-agrawal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/miki-agrawal/</guid>
      <description>*Miki Agrawal wrote the book, Do Cool Sh*t. This is a short transcription of jam-packed advice on starting a business.*
Miki has a direct, no nonsense approach. Her stories are powerful and eye-opening. The video is super high-energy and full of quick, actionable advice. Check it out here.
Purpose 0:31 Purpose is your best motivation. If you&amp;rsquo;re starting a business to make money. It&amp;rsquo;s not going to work.
If you&amp;rsquo;re starting a business that has a purpose, you can stand the test of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Omar Zenhom</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/omar-zenhom/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/omar-zenhom/</guid>
      <description>Omar Zenhom shares a quick review of Edward de Bono&amp;rsquo;s book, Six Thinking Hats, on the $100 MBA podcast. The framework presented by de Bono is practical and useful when making decisions.
Listen to Zenhom&amp;rsquo;s 15 minute review here, and check out a short transcription and graphic below.
Why the Framework? 2:40 As Edward de Bono explains in his book, thinking is the ultimate human resource. Yet, we can never be satisfied with our most important skill.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beth Dunn</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/beth-dunn/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/beth-dunn/</guid>
      <description>Beth Dunn shares how to use your words. You&amp;rsquo;ve likely heard her 10 tips before. But Beth really explains these in detail with techniques on how and why to do these things.
She believes we don&amp;rsquo;t spend enough time thinking about how we sound. We only think about why we want to say. Check out the excerpt below and 10 tips at the bottom of this post. Watch the talk here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>James Yancey</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/j-dilla/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/j-dilla/</guid>
      <description>James Yancey aka J Dilla deserves to be in the same sentence as John Coltrane and Miles Davis.
J Dilla joins Gilles Peterson&amp;rsquo;s World Wide in 2001 to speak on several tracks from his solo album, Welcome 2 Detroit, and other collaboration and production tidbits. Listen to the 30 minute interview here and read the transcription below.
Welcome to Detroit 2:59 Well the title Welcome 2 Detroit is welcoming you to Detroit!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rachel Andrew</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/rachel-andrew/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/rachel-andrew/</guid>
      <description>This is a 45-minute talk from Rachel Andrew. Rachel is the co-founder of the CMS, Perch. She shares lessons learned from supporting customers and building a business.
I found myself nodding in agreement multiple times while listening to Rachel. As someone who works in customer support, this felt like a much needed pep talk to me. Check out Rachel&amp;rsquo;s other talks, writing, presentations, and books here. Watch and listen to the full Industry Conference talk here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manoj Bhargava</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/manoj-bhargava/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/manoj-bhargava/</guid>
      <description>Take a half-hour and listen to this talk from Manoj Bhargava. Manoj is founder of 5-Hour Energy, a philanthropist, and full of wisdom. The story behind the product is fascinating and Manoj&amp;rsquo;s common sense will smack your right across the face.
Thanks to Ryan Singer (@rjs) for sharing a link to the talk months ago. Watch and listen here.
Two ways to get technology 1:05 There are only two ways to get technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saya Hillman</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/saya-hillman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/saya-hillman/</guid>
      <description>Saya Hillman. All I can say is I&amp;rsquo;m a fan. This is one of the first episodes of David Kadavy&amp;rsquo;s fantastic new podcast, Love Your Work. Saya shares how she started her own company after being fired, how she defines her own success, and how to find your own superpowers.
A few excerpts are below and you can listen to the hour long conversation here.
How did Mac &amp;amp; Cheese Productions start?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>William Ury</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/william-ury/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/william-ury/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation between William Ury and Simon Sinek. The two discuss Ury&amp;rsquo;s new book, Getting to Yes with Yourself, and other negotiation tips.
It&amp;rsquo;s a dense back-and-forth, so you might find yourself rewinding the video a bit like I did. Sinek adds a lot with his questions (listen to his TED talk if you haven&amp;rsquo;t before) and shares his own experiences too. Check out the excerpt below and the video here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julie Zhuo</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/julie-zhuo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/julie-zhuo/</guid>
      <description>Julie Zhuo chats with Bryn Jackson and Brian Lovin of the Design Details podcast. Julie shares her path from being Facebook&amp;rsquo;s first intern to leading design on a product that is used by billions of people.
Below is a transcribed excerpt, but the whole interview is full of useful advice. Be sure to check out some of Julie&amp;rsquo;s writing too :)
What is being a manager about? Over the years, what I really enjoy is working with designers and really helping designers become better designers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Maney</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kevin-maney/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kevin-maney/</guid>
      <description>This is a lecture Kevin Maney delivered at the Kenan-Flager Business School at UNC-Chapel Hill in 2009. Kevin talks through the trade offs we constantly make between fidelity and convenience. If you want more on this topic, check out his book Trade-Off.
Lots to digest here and some marvelous examples that will make you think. It&amp;rsquo;s a two part video, check out excerpts and links below.
 Part 1 Part 2  What is Trade off?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Torrey Podmajersky</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/torrey-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/torrey-p/</guid>
      <description>This a talk delivered by Torrey Podmajersky at the 2015 Write the Docs conference. Torrey is a UI writer for Microsoft. She has worked on Xbox and other projects that are used by millions of people. Torrey sprinkles in dynamite examples about how to keep people moving when using your product. Check out the full video here and excerpts below.
What is UI Text? 00:56 I&amp;rsquo;m going to tell you about these two cars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merlinn Mann</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/merlinn-mann/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/merlinn-mann/</guid>
      <description>Merlin Mann shares some wisdom in this talk delivered at the E4E Developer Conference in 2014. It&amp;rsquo;s inspiring, funny, honest, damn good advice on how to get better at whatever you do. Below are excerpts, but the entire talk is worth a watch and listen.
Better is elusive: 3:20 I find it very hard to get better at things. I find it very difficult to do. I think a lot of people struggle with it for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessica Lawrence </title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jessica-lawrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jessica-lawrence/</guid>
      <description>Jessica Lawrence shares a story about leadership. From high school to the Girl Scouts of the USA to NY Tech Meetup, Jessica connects the dots about what is needed to be a leader. I was directed to this video by Jeff Vincent. Check out his newsletter and subscribe here.
And take 10 minutes to listen to Jessica&amp;rsquo;s story.
Doing What You Think is Right Most of the time when I was in high school, it was a good thing to be featured in the school newspaper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samuel Hulick</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/samuel-hulick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Nov 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/samuel-hulick/</guid>
      <description>This is conversation between Samuel Hulick and Justin Jackson on Product People TV. Samuel shares how he built User Onboarding and what he&amp;rsquo;s learned along the way. Lots of useful examples of how to treat customers like human beings. Check out the full conversation here.
##How Did You Start User Onboarding
My friend Jane Portman has an analogy that I use all the time, which is &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s like having your suitcase packed with no handle on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pamela Slim</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/pamela-slim/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/pamela-slim/</guid>
      <description>This a conversation between Pamela Slim and Sean Blanda on the 99U podcast. Lately, if I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about reading a certain book, I&amp;rsquo;ll look for a podcast or interview with the author to learn more about it. This a perfect example.
Sean and Pamela discuss her book, Body of Work: Finding the Thread That Ties Your Story Together. After listening, I&amp;rsquo;ve added this one to my list to read in the near future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob Moesta</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/bob-moesta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/bob-moesta/</guid>
      <description>Bob Moesta is the &amp;ldquo;Milkshake Man.&amp;rdquo; He&amp;rsquo;s a designer, engineer, and businessman. He&amp;rsquo;s known for the Jobs-to-be-Done approach to business. Bob is who Clayton Christensen calls for advice on this idea.
Check out a slew of examples below and listen to the full conversation with Bob and Horace Dediu on the Critical Path podcast.
Example: Snickers vs. Milky Way Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the candy isle. For example, the Snickers and the Milky Way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gina Redish</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gina-redish/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gina-redish/</guid>
      <description>Ginny Redish is the author of Letting Go of the Words: Writing Web Content that Works. She is a pioneer in how to communicate on the web. Ginny has helped companies like IBM communicate with customers and teaches people why content is conversation.
Check out the full conversation with her and Kristina Halvorson on the Content Talks podcast. And find a short excerpt below.
Content as Conversation If you think about it, in a typical website, your site just doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist until somebody comes to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kevin Kelly</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kevin-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kevin-kelly/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s a conversation between Tim Ferriss and Kevin Kelly on the Tim Ferriss Show. A college dropout, Kevin shares his story of living overseas, doing LSD at 50 years old, and what he&amp;rsquo;s learned along the way. Kevin is the Senior Maverick at Wired Magazine and known for other projects like Cool Tools.
Below is an excerpt of a three-part conversation. It just scratches the surface. Make sure you listen to all three parts, as Ferriss says, &amp;ldquo;Kevin Kelly might be the real-life Most Interesting Man In The World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jenn Lim</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jenn-lim/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jenn-lim/</guid>
      <description>This is a talk with Jenn Lim on the 33 Voices podcast. Jenn is a a former consultant to Zappos and created the Zappos Culture Book. She later helped launch Tony Hsieh&amp;rsquo;s book, Delivering Happiness, and since transformed that concept into a company. Today, Jenn is the CEO and Chief Happiness Officer at Delivering Happiness. Listen to the full podcast here and check out the excerpt below.
Misconceptions about Happiness It&amp;rsquo;s not all about rainbows and unicorns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Allan Branch</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/allan-branch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/allan-branch/</guid>
      <description>This is a presentation from Allan Branch. Allan is the co-founder of Less Accounting. He shares his story and the family businesses that influenced him along the way.
After reading this excerpt, you&amp;rsquo;ll want to high five Allan. It&amp;rsquo;s incredible advice. Check out his site Massalina Drive and follow along with the presentation at these two links: part one and part two.
##5 Things My Parents Taught Me About Business</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nicole Fenton</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/nicole-fenton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/nicole-fenton/</guid>
      <description>Nicole Fenton is a guest on the Happy Monday Podcast with Josh Long and Sarah Parmenter. Nicole designs with words. She is excellent communicator working with companies from Apple to Facebook. The trio talks her book, Nicely Said, co-authored with Kate Kiefer Lee and other philosophies behind writing. Listen to the full conversation here.
Starting from the bottom I knew I wanted to be a writer when I was very young.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scott Stratten</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/scott-stratten/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/scott-stratten/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation between Scott Stratten and Todd Henry on the Accidental Creative podcast. The two rant and discuss how to show empathy in marketing and his book QR Codes Kill Kittens. Listen to the full conversation here.
Unmarketing 12 years ago we formed the company to market the way people wanted to be marketed to. It was created out of, I was just fed up with hypocritical marketing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Valerie Coulton</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/valerie-coulton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/valerie-coulton/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation between Alistair Croll and Valerie Coulton via Tilt the Windmill. Valerie is an Innovation Catalyst at Schibsted Classified Media. She tells her story of moving to Barcelona and how her background in customer service has helped lead change in organizations. The excerpt is focused on the first 20 minutes, but hang on for more talk about disruption and lean analytics. Check out the full audio here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derek Sivers</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/derek-sivers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/derek-sivers/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation between Bob Baker and Derek Sivers on The Creative Entrepreneur podcast. Derek shares his background from circus ringleader to musician to million-dollar business owner at CD Baby to creating a book publishing company. You can learn a lot from his perspective and his book Anything You Want. Check out an excerpt below and watch or listen to the full conversation here.
Changing Your Operating System I&amp;rsquo;m a total Chicago boy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rena Tom</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/rena-tom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/rena-tom/</guid>
      <description>This is a Pencil vs. Pixel conversation between Rena Tom and Cesar Contreras. Pencil vs. Pixel, hosted by Cesar, is a weekly web show that shares insight, advice, and inspiration about creative work. Rena is a consultant and the market editor for Anthology magazine. Plus she is the founder of Makeshift Society, a clubhouse and creative co-working space in San Francisco and Brooklyn. Check out an excerpt below and listen to the full conversation as Rena shares her story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brad Frost</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/brad-frost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/brad-frost/</guid>
      <description>The following is a TEDx talk with Brad Frost. The web designer, writer, and speaker delivers a perspective about why you should share what you create across the web. You should check out his blog and his Death to Bullshit talk about craft. Check out the full TEDx video here.
How the Web Changed Creation Because it was so expensive to create, the focus was always on the final product.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maria Popova</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/maria-popova/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/maria-popova/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation from the Employee of the Month podcast. Catie Lazarus and Maria Popova talk through life and learning. Popova curates an amazing blog called Brain Pickings and runs a discovery engine called Explore. It&amp;rsquo;s impossible not to find inspiration in her work and this talk. Listen to the full 45 minute conversation here and check out excerpts below.
How did Brain Pickings Start? What I do always has two components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clayton Christensen</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/clayton-christensen/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/clayton-christensen/</guid>
      <description>This is a short excerpt from a conversation between Clayton Christensen and Tom Ashbrook on the On Point NPR radio show. Christensen is the co-author of How to Measure Your Life, a book that uses business and real-life examples to teach you lessons. Sandwiched between religious and political sidebars, there is thought-provoking conversation as Christensen answers questions from the audience. Listen to the full conversation here.
Where You Spend Your Resources Toyota didn&amp;rsquo;t come to America with the Lexus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ashley Verrill</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/ashley-verrill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/ashley-verrill/</guid>
      <description>This excerpt is a little off the beaten path. But if you&amp;rsquo;ve ever received bad customer service or if you work in customer service, you will find it useful. It&amp;rsquo;s a conversation between Ashley Verrill and Chase Clemons on the Support Ops Podcast.
Ashley is a managing editor at Software Advice where she runs Customer Service Investigator. Her work has been featured across TechCrunch, Gigaom, and Wired. Listen to the full podcast here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Fried</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jason-fried/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jason-fried/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from Chicago Founders&amp;rsquo; Stories. Jason Fried shares the the story behind 37 Signals, Basecamp, and working with Jeff Bezos. Thanks to Pat Ryan and builtinchicago.org. Watch the entire interview here. The transcript starts at 1:18:30.
 I love listening to him, more than talking to him. I will give you one business thing and one life thing he told us.
 Business The most important thing in business is to figure out what&amp;rsquo;s not going to change in your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tina Roth Eisenberg</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/tina-roth-eisenberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/tina-roth-eisenberg/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from a 2-part series on mentor lessons with Tina Roth Eisenberg. Tina shares tips to success for Shopify&amp;rsquo;s 2013 Build a Business Competition. Special thanks to Shopify for hosting the video. Watch part 1 and part 2.
The Best Way to Complain Don&amp;rsquo;t be a complainer, make things better. I have this personal rule that if I find myself complaining about this same thing over and over again, I need to either let it go or do something about it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peter Coughter</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/peter-coughter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/peter-coughter/</guid>
      <description>This is a conversation between Peter Coughter and Mitch Joel for the Six Pixels of Separation Podcast. Coughter is the author of The Art of the Pitch, a professor at the VCU Brandcenter, and an advertising consultant. Check out an excerpt below, and listen to the full talk here.
Nervous and Scared Yesterday morning, I was in my car and I was listening to a sports talk show. And we can learn things from all kinds of different places by the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debbie Millman</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/debbie-millman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/debbie-millman/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from a conversation between Debbie Millman and Jonathan Fields for the Good Life Project. Millman shares her career path and wisdom on how to find purpose in your life. Watch and listen to the full episode here.
Do what you want I teach seniors in college. And my class is about getting a job. But it&amp;rsquo;s about getting the job of your dreams. Not just getting a job to pay the rent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ezra Firestone</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/ezra-firestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/ezra-firestone/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from the eCommerceFuel podcast with Andrew Youderian and Ezra Firestone. Ezra shares his unique story from poker player turned entrepreneur, and how to market a product with messaging. Listen to the full interview here.
How to get what you want I believe you get what you want from people who have it. If you want to run an eCommerce store, you find someone like you - and you learn it from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jessica Hische</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jessica-hische/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/jessica-hische/</guid>
      <description>This is a Creative Mornings talk with Jessica Hische in Vancouver. Hische delivers about a 10 minute rant sans slides that is amazing. The majority of the excerpt is in the beginning, but you hang on for a great conversation about type. Watch and listen to the full video here.
Mandatory Everyone knows as soon as you make something mandatory, it becomes the opposite of what you want to do for a living.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stanley Hainsworth</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/stanley-hainsworth/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/stanley-hainsworth/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from a 2010 conversation between Stanley Hainsworth and Robert Scoble. Hainsworth shares his path to storytelling and his agency Tether. Special thanks to Scoble and Rackspace for hosting the video. Watch the full conversation here.
Brands are People I always equate brands as people. You could describe what Apple is as a person. Because of the personality they&amp;rsquo;ve created.
So with companies, the first thing I do is say lets figure out what your story is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Sierra</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kathy-sierra/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/kathy-sierra/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from 2010 Gov 2.0 Expo with Kathy Sierra. She has given this talk several times and spread the message on her blog. Special thanks to O&amp;rsquo;Reilly Media for hosting the video. Watch the full talk here.
Kicking Ass Where there is passion, there are people kicking ass. People don&amp;rsquo;t sustain passion for things they continue to suck at.
One of the reasons that passion is compelling for people is because when they are pursing something, learning and growing - they start to have a higher resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from the 1997 Apple Worldwide Developers Conference. An hour long Q &amp;amp; A, it includes nuggets of brilliance that still are true 17 years later. Special thanks to mactechlab for posting it to YouTube, and to Semil for sharing the video. Watch the full talk here.
Focus: 5:55 When you think about focusing, you think focusing is saying yes. Focusing is about saying no. Focusing is about saying no.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amy Hoy</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/amy-hoy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/amy-hoy/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from a conversation between Justin Jackson and Amy Hoy. The two discuss building an audience and a product people actually want. You don&amp;rsquo;t have to bootstrap alone. Listen to the full conversation here.
You&amp;rsquo;re Not Important I think everybody is every field thinks they are the ones who are critical to the success of the product. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a designer, writer, marketing type stuff - every single audience I&amp;rsquo;ve been in, has said we&amp;rsquo;re the ones who are so important.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gary Vaynerchuk</title>
      <link>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gary-vee/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://people.hotdogsandeggs.com/gary-vee/</guid>
      <description>The following is an excerpt from the 2014 SXSW Keynote with Gary Vaynerchuk. Special thanks to SXSW for hosting the video, and to Gary for answering tons of questions. This is uncensored and includes lots of expletives. It&amp;rsquo;s fucking fantastic. Watch the full keynote here.
Technology &amp;amp; Time If you&amp;rsquo;re an entrepreneur, you should spend lots of time at night thinking about where there is inefficiency in our society and where technology can solve that problem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>